export default function Data() {
	return [
		{
			id: 0,
			level: "Easy",
			series: "F.R.I.E.N.D.S.",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What does Joey not share?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Money", "Room", "Food", "Friends"],
			answer: "Food",
		},
		{
			id: 1,
			level: "Difficult",
			series: "How I Met Your Mother",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What is Ted's Middle Name?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Rosalind", "Evelyn", "Marylin", "Stevenson"],
			answer: "Evelyn",
		},
		{
			id: 2,
			level: "Easy",
			series: "The Big Bang Theory",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What is Howard?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Astronaut", "Engineer", "Father", "All of the above"],
			answer: "All of the above",
		},
		{
			id: 3,
			level: "Medium",
			series: "Suits",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText:
				"Which Institute's graduates are only allowed in Pearson Specter Litt?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Princeton", "Cambridge", "Stanford", "Harvard"],
			answer: "Harvard",
		},
		{
			id: 4,
			level: "Medium",
			series: "How I Met Your Mother",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What is Lily and Marshall's son's Middle Name?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Wait For It", "Go Through It", "See To It", "Go For It"],
			answer: "Wait For It",
		},
		{
			id: 5,
			level: "Difficult",
			series: "Modern Family",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What is Jay and Gloria's son's full name?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: [
				"Joe Prichett",
				"Fulgencio Joseph Prichett",
				"Jay Prichett Junior",
				"None of the above",
			],
			answer: "Fulgencio Joseph Prichett",
		},
		{
			id: 6,
			level: "Easy",
			series: "Brooklyn Nine-Nine",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "Why does Jake's towel not catch on fire?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: [
				"Because it is fire proof",
				"Because it was mistakenly cut from fire department's materials ",
				"Because it never fully dries",
				"Trick question, he does not have a towel",
			],
			answer: "Because it never fully dries",
		},
		{
			id: 7,
			level: "Easy",
			series: "Game of Thrones",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: `What do you feel when people watching season 1 say, "Ned Stark is going to be King at end"?`,
			questionImage: "",
			options: [
				"Sorry for them",
				"Secret Laughter",
				"Sure buddy with air quotes",
				"All of the above",
			],
			answer: "All of the above",
		},
		{
			id: 8,
			level: "Difficult",
			series: "How to get away with Murder",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText:
				"Ok, let's get serious again, What is Laurel's child's name?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: ["Cristopher", "Wesley", "Chris", "Jhonny"],
			answer: "Cristopher",
		},
		{
			id: 9,
			level: "Easy",
			series: "Sherlock",
			questionType: "text",
			questionText: "What is Sherlock's biggest enemy's name?",
			questionImage: "",
			options: [
				"Mycroft Holmes",
				"Jim Moriarty",
				"D.I. Lestrade",
				"Molly Hooper",
			],
			answer: "Jim Moriarty",
		},
	];
}